Aizaz Hassan

Islāmābād, Pakistan



aizazhassan@mail.com



03235111244



linkedin.com/in/aizazulhassan

Summary

With experience as a project coordinator and cyber reconnaissance and combat I have the ability to successfully manage complex projects and develop strategies to protect against cyber threats. I am keen on learning new skills and implementing them in the workplace. I enjoy working in a diverse environment and being able to work to high standards is one of my qualities.

Experience



Ü Cyber Reconnaissance and Combat

Bahria University

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

- Made cyber reconnaissance and combat centers project netspection
- · Managed servers with PHP, SQL and XAMP
- Conducted Bahria Student Development Cyber Security Courses
- Trained new up coming junior Computer Science students for Internships at Bahria Innovation center
- Modified packet inspections user interface and designs



Assistant Project Coordinator

Calyx Pakistan

Jun 2021 - Oct 2021 (5 months)

- Communicated with stakeholders regarding project needs and goals
- · Worked with excel using VBA to modify functions and automating actions
- Worked with Power BI for data visualization on excel
- Supported the coordination and management of projects
- · Contributed to the planning and development of projects
- Researched information as required
- · Performed administrative tasks such as preparing invoices, estimates, scheduling meetings, etc
- Kept track of and reported on project progress
- Completed any tasks assigned by the Project Manager



Customer Service Associate

Caylx Foundation

Nov 2019 - May 2020 (7 months)

- · Contacted O/A levels schools all over Pakistan
- Back and fro communication with O/A levels schools representatives
- · Provided outstanding customer service
- Attended training sessions to grow knowledge of products and to develop customer service skills

Education

‡ Bahria University

Bachelor of Computer Science Aug 2019 - Jun 2023

Roots International Schools & Colleges

A levels, Computer Science Jun 2016 - 2018

Joan Mcdonald School

O Levels, Sciences Jun 2014 - Apr 2016

Licenses & Certifications

- Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) SCRUMstudy Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile
- Certificate of Advanced Training on Today's Youth Tomorrow Leaders Fahad Khan Research International

Skills

SQL • Web Development • C++ • Python (Programming Language) • Project Management • Communication • Strategy • Analytical Skills • Design • Data Analysis